Today, please, we're going to start with
part one, talking about morning
routines. My tea, tell me, do you
usually have the same morning routine
every day?
>> Um, I usually take it day by day, I
think. I don't know, I feel like having
too rigid of a schedule doesn't help me
um kind of prepare for the day. Like I
It just depends on what obligations I
have that day, but I'm pretty like early
riser morning person, so uh a lot of the
time I tend to wake up at like 6:00 to
do some work instead of doing work late
into the night. It just works a lot
better for my schedule, and so um it It
really just depends on how much work I
have on a given day, but I don't like to
stick to
routines.
>> Thank you very much.
What do you usually do when you first
wake up?
>> Honestly, look at my phone.
>> [gasps and laughter]
>> Cuz I don't know, it's where um my
family contacts me, it's where I get all
of like um emails related to school and
stuff like that, so like all the
important stuff, so that it kind of like
if I'm doing work in the morning, it
kind of gets me in the mood like get
more productive if I'm already thinking
about these things and like like laying
out everything I have to do for the day.
So.
>> Fantastic. Thank you. How's your morning
routine changed since you were younger?
>> Yeah, it used to be a lot more chaotic
because me and [clears throat] my
brother like to sleep in a lot, so then
we would wake up a lot later than we
were supposed to for school, and so it'd
be like one big rush. But nowadays, um
since I can control my own schedule a
little better, I can like plan it around
my own moods and whatever, so it isn't
as rushed, but I do think having those
like um
schedules in my childhood helped me
um
like wake up on time, for example, and
like know what I need to do to begin my
my
but like I It's a very different mood.
>> Thank you very much. Let's move on now
to talk about crowded places. Is your
city a crowded place?
>> That's an understatement.
>> [laughter]
>> There's about I think like 10 million
residents in the city and so it's like
always really busy. There's like hustle
and bustle. You can't avoid people no
matter where you go, really.
>> Yeah, definitely. Thank you. I agree.
How do you feel when you spend time in a
crowded place?
>> Um I think it's because I grew up in a
city, but I it really doesn't affect me
at all. I like like the anonymity of it.
Like you can just flow through it like a
crowd. Like I think of it and many
people describe it as like a river where
you can just navigate through crowds of
people and like
um there's like a shared understanding
that like okay, you try not to bump into
people. You don't like stare at someone
for too long, for example. So I feel
really at home when I'm in a crowded
place.
>> Thank you. And finally, let's talk about
sports. Mighty, have you ever played a
sport? [clears throat]
>> A couple, yeah.
Um I did basketball, swimming,
badminton. Like there's just like a
variety of stuff I tried, but yeah.
[clears throat]
>> Which was your favorite?
>> Personally, badminton. I've been going
to like um a club meeting every Tuesday
recently where we just play like
recreationally. So it yeah, it gets
exercise in.
>> Thank you. And
finally, are there any sports that are
particularly popular in your country?
>> I would say the most popular one is
soccer or football
because I don't know.
Like with the World Cup going on right
now, it's just really just a big stir.
So then yeah, I think it's the most
popular one because it's also so easy to
play. Like you really just need a ball
and like maybe two trees in the
background for a goal post. But yeah.
>> Why is that important in Vietnam? If it
means simple to play.
>> Um I think
because like
well, now there's a lot more options and
like stuff, but many people came from
the countryside or like in times of
struggle. So then
um they needed like those quick ways to
entertain themselves and also have fun
as kids and like go out and like
interact with people. So it's like a
social bonding event and also like
exercise for kids. So then you just took
whatever you could and like scrap
together some fun game.
>> Yeah. Thank you. That's one of the
reasons I love Vietnam. Yeah, wonderful.
Okay, let's move on to part number two
now, please. And I've got a question for
you here and you'll have 1 minute to
prepare. The question is, could you
please describe a time you received
exceptionally good customer service from
a business or company?
Fantastic. So that brings us to the end
of the 1 minute now, My Thi. So when
you're ready, please can you start?
>> Um I would say a time I received
exceptionally good customer service was
at Rock Water Bay in Phan Thiet. I think
they changed their name since then, but
my family used to go there often because
um
we're like an animal-lover family. We
have like a couple pets and such. So
when we first a lot of resorts in the
area don't allow like animals. So then
when we first came to them with like a
dog carrier bag, they were a little
shocked, to be honest.
>> [laughter]
>> But then they were pretty accommodating,
actually. It wasn't uh the most
professional, but the receptionist was
like, "Okay,
if you keep the noise down to minimum,
if you don't make a mess, you can have
your dog there." So then that was a
really memorable vacation because
otherwise we would have had to like
drive home or like find a hostel
to stay in. But like because we got to
have our pets there and they were so
accommodating to what we needed, it like
made my family kind of instantly fall in
love with the place. Like it wasn't
exceptional in its like um facilities or
like any of its
location, but because the staff were so
like personable and friendly,
um
we just kept coming back and eventually
my dad is still best friends with the
old security guard there actually
>> [laughter]
>> because he we they used to chat by like
the poolside while me and my brother
like played in there and like splashed
each other. And
a lot of the staff began to like know us
by name because it was so like
it was we just kept coming back to it.
It was really special. But like
otherwise, they were just
they helped us a lot with like we
um my mom lost her beach towel. So then
there was like a small convenience store
to the side. They walked us all the way
there and
>> [laughter]
>> and started haggling with the shop lady
to get better pricing because it was a
little overpriced for like a
China touristy area.
And I feel like it really like made me
value like being friendly and making
good first impressions to
customers.
>> Ah, thank you very much. That sounds
like an amazing experience. If I can
have your sheet back now. Thank you so
much. Well done.
Mighty, I want to continue in part three
talking about that kind of topic. Um
can you tell me in a competitive market,
is a company's customer service just as
important as the actual product or
price?
>> I feel like the most important part
would be like the quality of the product
that they're offering, but I do think
that customer service is extremely like
a vital part because it's like the first
impression and also the face of the
company. And since like nowadays there's
a lot of competitors with very similar
quality products, I feel like customer
service has become increasingly
important when dealing with customers
because it's just like
how you market the products and how you
get customers to stay and like trust the
brand. So, it's pretty important.
>> Okay, well then.
As automated chatbots and AI customer
service become a standard, what unique
value do human customer service officers
provide?
>> I think like I said in my previous
answer about the resort, I think it's
that like authenticity that makes it
really really special because
um
like AI chatbots, they're running on
programs and
like they're adapting and they're
learning, but they only go as far as
their code and like how much they've
learned. While humans, they can adapt
more easily, they problem-solve, and
they're able to like
convey meaning in a like more meaningful
meaningful way. But yeah, I think even
with AI chatbots, you need like super
human supervisors like constantly
checking over the quality or whether or
not the bot has like messed up or it's
like accurate. So, I think humans are
really irreplaceable in those fields
because you still need a person behind
the AI chatbot to ensure that it is a
good service.
So.
>> Yeah, very interesting. Thank you. Let's
move on to a different topic now about
street markets. My team, why do
traditional street markets remain
popular even in modern cities with large
supermarkets?
>> I think part of it is like the
familiarity of it because when you go to
the market, you're seeing all these
sellers face-to-face and you know they
get a lot of like their produce from
local farmers and stuff. So, then some
people value like that um like
small-scale
economic contribution and just like
supporting and giving back to their
community. I think for most people it's
a matter of like tradition because it's
just like something your grandma did,
something your great-grandmother did.
You went to the market in the morning,
you bought the meat for the day, you
bought the rice for the day. And so you
get to know all these people over like
decades and decades and they kind of
become family friends in the end. And so
yeah, it's that like and supermarkets
are still relatively new to the climate,
so then
people are like
less trusting of like the goods they
produce because it does feel like kind
of cold and clinical sometimes compared
to like seeing the sellers face to face.
And another benefit is being able to
haggle at the market, so you can track
like how
things are like changing in time like
the inflation and such. And so it's just
yeah.
>> Fantastic. And I guess it's part of the
culture in Vietnam as well.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. Wonderful. Thank you. But do you
think local government should invest in
preserving traditional public spaces or
should they prioritize modern commercial
real estate?
>> I think absolutely like the
public places should be preserved
because in a way they are like a
cultural heritage and they're a
reflection of not just where we came
from but like who we are nowadays
because like
I think to pave over all that stuff and
just build like office building on
office building, it seems like erasing
that part of our history. For example, I
remember driving with my mom past a road
one day and there was this beautiful
like Chinese-style like ancient
Chinese-style building with like French
murals on it and it was being um
it was being torn down to make space for
like a new office building or like
apartment. And I just felt like in that
moment it was such a shame to see that
part kind of like literally buried under
rubble.
And
yeah, to have something new just like be
placed on it. I feel like
I do feel like there's like a kind of
soul or spirit or like history to that
place.
And yeah.
It just erases your identity when you
tear it down.
>> Exactly. Thank you so much. And finally,
can you tell me in what ways do outdoor
commercial spaces like markets
contribute to the social fabric of a
neighborhood?
>> I think like again, it builds up that
community. And I think um
like making a soccer ball to go outside,
you
kind of start to bond with the people
around you. And it encourages you to go
outside and make all of these
connections cuz in the end humans are
like pack animals. We value all of our
relationships and like the way
we connect with each other, so I just
feel like
it's really vital to have those spaces.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Well done. And
that brings us to the end of the test.
Congratulations.
>> Well done. Good job. Thank you.
>> Matey, I just would like to ask you a
few questions. How do you feel that
went? How did you feel during the test?
>> I feel like I rambled a little bit, but
>> [laughter]
>> it was fine. It was mostly on topic. I
forgot the last question halfway through
my answer.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay. But you did the right thing.
Instead of panicking and just saying
nothing, you you totally paused and then
just stopped there at the same time.
Yeah, amazing. One thing that I'm blown
away by, I know that you've spent time
abroad in the States, and so your
fluency is fantastic. I think that the
way that you answered the part three
questions was phenomenal in the sense
that I really tried to adjust the
questions to make them a bit more
difficult, but you seemed to handle them
with grace, which Which great. Yeah.
It seemed like actually your part three
was the best.
Better than your part one, which is kind
of like the reverse, role reversal. I
feel like you'd warmed up for the part
three.
>> Yeah, a little bit. I Yeah, starting
with morning routines was hard. There's
not much you can speak about.
>> Yeah. Well, overall I thought you did a
great performance and I want to say a
big thank you for joining us today. Good
job. Thank you,
very nice to meet you. Come on.
>> [music]